...
I like digging holes and hiding things inside them
When I'll grow old I hope I won't forget to find them
'Cause I've got memories and travel like gypsies in the night
I built a home and wait for someone to tear it down
Then pack it up in boxes, head for the next town running
'Cause I've got memories and travel like gypsies in the night
And a thousand times I've seen this road
A thousand times
I've got no roots, but my home was never on the ground
I've got no roo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oots
I like standing still, boy, that's just a wishful plan
Ask me where I come from, I'll say a different land
But I've got memories and travel like gypsies in the night
I count gate's and numbers, then play the guessing game
It's just the place that changes, the rest is still the same
But I've got memories and travel like gypsies in the night
And a thousand times I've seen this road
A thousand times
I've got no roots, but my home was never on the ground
I've got no roo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oots
I like digging holes
Hiding things inside them
When I'll grow old
I won't forget to find them
I like digging holes
Hiding things inside them
When I'll grow old
I won't forget to find them
(I'VE GOT NO ROOTS)
(NO ROOTS)
I've got no roots, but my home was never on the ground
I've got no roo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oots
(NO!)